ecomii.com 2008-12-18

# ecomii Privacy Policy

The following Privacy Policy summarizes the various ways that Ecomii, LLC (“Service Provider,” “we”, “our” and “us”) treats the information you provide while accessing the website pages located at the URL ecomii.com and the subdomains thereof (collectively, the “Website”). It is our goal to bring you information that is tailored to your individual needs and, at the same time, protect your privacy. 

Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. You can access the Privacy Policy any time at http://www.ecomii.com/privacy-policy. Your use of and/or registration on any aspect of the Website will constitute your agreement to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website. This Privacy Policy does not cover information collected elsewhere, including without limitation offline and on sites linked to from the Website.

In addition to reviewing this Privacy Policy, please read our Terms of Use. Your use of the Website constitutes agreement to the terms and conditions of the Terms of Use as well.

We may modify this Privacy Policy from time to time, so you should regularly check the Privacy Policy for updates and revisions. In consideration of your continued access to the Website you agree to any updates or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

 **I. INFORMATION COLLECTED BY US**

We generally collect personally identifiable information about you through the Website with your consent. For instance, when you enter a sweepstakes or contest, complete a survey, make a purchase, subscribe to our publication(s), or register for any portion of our services, you are asked to provide information such as your e-mail address, name or phone number. Other information such as your age or gender may also be requested.

Additionally, our servers may also automatically collect information about your computer when you visit the Website, including without limitation the type of browser software you use, the operating system you are running, the website that referred you, and your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address. Your IP address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your university.

 **II. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION**

We use personally identifiable information you supply through the Website to provide you with goods and services offered through the Website. We may also use the information you provide to us to communicate with you about new features, products or services, and/or to improve the services that we offer.

We may sell or share your personally identifiable information with our affiliates and with businesses that we think can offer you services and products that may be of interest to you. If you do not wish to have your personally identifiable information shared, let us know by writing to us at the address set forth at the end of this Privacy Policy. If you do not wish to receive future commercial communications from us by e-mail, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions contained within the e-mail or let us know by writing to us at the address set forth at the end of this Privacy Policy. If you have any other concerns relating to your personally identifiable information, please contact our Privacy Policy Coordinator at the address listed below to advise of your concerns.

In addition to the above, we also permit third parties that provide services in connection with the Website to access to our databases which contain your personally identifiable information, but only for the purpose of providing those services. Further, if you make purchases through the Website, we may forward your information to third parties who provide services in connection with processing such purchase orders. We may also provide your information to our advertisers to assist them in serving advertisements that more closely match your interests.

While we will seek to require third parties who have access to your information to follow appropriate privacy policies and will not authorize them to use this information except for the express purpose for which it is provided, we do not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties. There may also be instances when we are legally required to provide access to our database in order to cooperate with investigations or legal proceedings.

In addition, we reserve the right to use the information we collect about your computer, which may at times be able to identify you, for any lawful business purpose, including without limitation to help diagnose problems with our servers, to gather broad demographic information, and to otherwise administer our Website.

While your personally identifiable information is protected as outlined above, we reserve the right to use, transfer, sell, and share aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible advertisers and partners.

Finally, from time to time we may sell some or all of our assets. In the event all or a portion of the assets owned or controlled by us, our parent or any subsidiary or affiliated entity are sold, assigned, transferred or acquired by another business, your information may be among the transferred assets.

 **III. COOKIES**

We may use “cookies” to control the display of ads, to track usage patterns on the site, to deliver editorial content, and to record registration and personal information. For example, if you register on any part of the Website and are given the option to save your user name and password on your computer, we can provide this convenience to you by placing a cookie on your computer. Our cookies may contain personally identifiable information and such cookies may be shared with our affiliates and other companies.

Some of our advertisers occasionally serve you cookies as well. We do not have control over cookies placed by advertisers.

If you don’t want any cookies, your Internet browser likely includes an option that allows you to not accept them. However, if you set your browser to refuse cookies, some portions of the Website may not function properly.

 **IV. KIDS AND PARENTS**

This Website is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas, forums or chats. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases, including subscriptions, on this site.

If your children disclose information about themselves in publicly accessible areas of the Website, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to do so.

If you’re worried about your children’s activities or their privacy on our site, we encourage you to e-mail our Privacy Policy Coordinator at privacy@ecomii.com.

 **V. PRIVACY POLICY COORDINATOR**

If you have other concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, you may also e-mail our Privacy Policy Coordinator. We welcome your feedback. You can also send us regular mail at the following address:

ECOMII, LLC  
Attention: Privacy Policy Coordinator

448 W. 16th Street5th Floor, Studio #4 New York, NY 10011privacy@ecomii.com
